Guide to the Cornell Law School photographs, 1974-1996.
Cornell Law School photographs, 1974-1996.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Law School photographs, 1974-1996.
18-1-2890.
Cornell Law School.
.6 cubic ft.
Photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Photographs of students, faculty, and visiting professors and lecturers.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photographs of students, faculty, and visiting professors and lecturers.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Law School.; Cornell Law School--Faculty.; Cornell Law School--Students.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Photographs
  - Student Candids (1989-1992) (Box 1)
  - Bullis, Fran (Box 1)
  - Smith, J.L. (Former Dean of Students) (Box 1)
  - Kunstler, William (VIP) (Box 1)
  - Kreilick, Kit (Associate Law Librarian) (Box 1)
  - Gunn, Alan (Box 1)
  - Oesterle, Dale A. (Box 1)
  - Williams, Susan (Box 1)
  - Williams, David (Box 1)
  - Zacharias, Fred C. (Box 1)
  - Berzon, Marsha (Visitor Fall 1994) (Box 1)
  - Bonnie, Richard J. (Visitor) (Box 1)
  - Craig, Paul (Box 1)
  - Diefenbach, D. Alan (Box 1)
  - Dolgin, Janet (Visitor Spring 1995) (Box 1)
  - Dripps, Donald (Visiting Prof) (Box 1)
  - Greenhouse, Carol (Director, Law and Society Program; Assistant Prof. Anthroplogy) (Box 1)
  - Hirschmann, Linda (Box 1)
  - Lane, Norman (Box 1)
  - Masson, Robin A. (Box 1)
  - Millon, David (Box 1)
  - Peterson, K. (Legal Aid) (Box 1)
  - Pozner, Daniel (Clinical Instructor) (Box 1)
  - Roth, Kristine (Visiting Prof) (Box 1)
  - Strong, Graham (Legal Aid) (Box 1)
  - Zaretsky, Barry (Box 1)
  - Zoller (Box 1)
  - Sullivan, Kathleen A. (Attorney) (Box 1)
  - Addis, Adeno (Box 2)
  - Akbus, Catherine (Box 2)
  - Blumkin, Joy (Box 2)
  - Branson (Box 2)
  - Bridge, Stuart (Visitor) (Box 2)
  - Cramton, Roger (Box 2)
  - Curtis, Richard (Visiting Prof) (Box 2)
  - Denicola, Robert (Box 2)
  - Dennis, Roger (Box 2)
  - Dolgin, Janet (Box 2)
  - Donahue, Charlie (Box 2)
  - Dzienkowski, John (Visitor - 1995) (Box 2)
  - Elson, Charles (Box 2)
  - Fajer, Marc (Box 2)
  - Fanto, James (Box 2)
  - Fentiman, Richard (Box 2)
  - Fernando, Gihan (Box 2)
  - Foster, Frances (Box 2)
  - Francioni, Francisco (Box 2)
  - Fuller, Betsey (Box 2)
  - Gerhardt, Michael (new in 1994) (Box 2)
  - Goldman, Pamela (Box 2)
  - Grant, Barbara (Box 2)
  - Green, Michael (Box 2)
  - Griffiths, A. (Box 2)
  - Hammond, Grant (Visiting Prof) (Box 2)
  - Holmes, Clive (Box 2)
  - Hutchinson (Box 2)
  - Kaye, David (Visiting Prof) (Box 2)
  - Kingsbury, Benedict (Box 2)
  - Loh, Wallace (Box 2)
  - LoPucki, Lynn (Box 2)
  - McChesney, Fred (Box 2)
  - McCord (Box 2)
  - McDougall, Harold (Box 2)
  - McIntyre, J. (Visitor) (Box 2)
  - Maclin, Tracey (Box 2)
  - Markesinis, Basil (Box 2)
  - Nance, Dale (Box 2)
  - Osgood, Russell (Box 2)
  - Rush, Sharon (Visitor) (Box 2)
  - Samuelson, Pamela (Box 2)
  - Shapiro, Harold (Box 2)
  - Simon, Bruce (Visiting Prof) (Box 2)
  - Slynn, Sir Gordon (Box 2)
  - Teson, Fernando (Visitor) (Box 2)
  - Thuronyi, Victor (Visiting Prof) (Box 2)
  - Wood, Diane (Box 2)
  - Staff and Faculty (Box 2)